Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Department of Theatre Records, 1911-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee Department of Theatre Records, 1911-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Department of Theatre
UWM Archival Collection 85
14.3 cubic ft. (23 boxes) 5 oversize folders 42 digital files (1.89 GB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
This collection contains UWM Theatre Department records consisting of alumni information, correspondence, performance planning, photographs, and programs from decades of plays and musicals performed by theater companies within the School of Fine Arts, including the Professional Theater Training Program and the University Players. Correspondence is largely between the chairs of the departments and faculty members regarding performance planning, budgeting, curriculum, and departmental activities. The correspondence from various countries details information on the several international programs the UWM theatre department participated in, including the International Theatre Festival and the World Theatre Training Institute. Faculty meeting minutes document curriculum changes, budgeting, and performance planning. Files include information on the foundation of the Theater Company (a company within the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee) and items regarding the Milwaukee Repertory Theater. Also included are production files, which contain performance budgets, set designs, programs, promotional materials, and performance reviews, as well as photographs, negatives, and slides. Items predating 1964 (the year of the department's creation) are programs and photographs of performances by players of University Theater, a drama club of UWM, and the Dramatic Club of the State Normal School.
Activity in the theater arts at UWM dates to 1911, when plays and musicals were given by the Dramatic Club and the senior class of the State Normal School. Prior to 1964, theater arts classes were taken through the Department of Speech. The Department of Theatre Arts officially began in the spring semester of 1964, two years after the formation of the School of Fine Arts. In 1982, the Department of Dance and the Department of Theatre Arts merged into one department. In 2003, the Department of Theatre and Dance split and became two separate departments once again.
Department of Theatre Arts Chairs
1964-1972 Corliss Phillabaum
1972-1976 Herb E. Felsenfeld
1976-1982 Sanford L. Robbins
Department of Theatre and Dance Chairs
1982-1988 Sanford L. Robbins
1988-1989 LeRoy L. Stoner
1989-1996 Malcolm J. Morrison
1996-2002 LeRoy L. Stoner
2002-2003 Ed Burgess
Department of Theatre Chairs
2003-2007 Pamela Rehberg
2007-2009 Bruce Brockman
2009- LeRoy L. Stoner
Department of Theatre Administrative Files contain records related to the department's management and administration. Included are correspondence, planning documents, faculty meeting minutes, alumni information, honorary society records, and department publicity. The Administrative Files also document events produced and promoted by the Theatre Department such as Summer in the Park, the International Theatre Festival, and production tours and trips.
Production files, organized by date, contain records of specific plays, musicals, or other performances. These files may contain programs, production notes, budgets, set and other production designs, posters, published reviews and play publicity. Some productions have corresponding blueprints. Production files also include performance photographs maintained in separate photograph files that are organized by date. Actor's headshots and program-related photographs are organized by subject and are maintained as part of the Administrative Files.
The records are arranged into the following series:
Administrative Files, 1946-2002
Production Files, 1911-2015
An inventory for all of the productions is available electronically in the Archives' case file.
Alternate Format
Selections from this collection are included in the UWM Libraries' digital collection, UWM Photo Collection.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Dance Records UWM Archival Collection 30
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Music Records UWM Archival Collection 84
UW-Milwaukee School of Fine Arts Records UWM Archival Collection 81
Deaccession Information
A Pabst Brewing Company poster was separated from accession 2015-009 and placed in the Pabst Brewing Company Records collection (UWM Mss 161) in an oversize folder.
Materials were separated from accessions 2015-009 and 2015-033 and placed in the UWM Peck School of Arts, Office of the Dean Records(UWM AC 81) as Box 28. A folder of records containing information on a performance by Theatre Sans Fil was transferred to Box 9 in the Student Union Collection (UWM AC 124). Several folders and a box of dance posters were transferred to the Dept of Dance Records (UWM AC 30).
Administrative/Restriction Information
Box 6 contains confidential student information that is restricted under the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA).
There are no access restrictions on the rest of the collection, which is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
As of October 10, 2016, all electronic files were accessible on an Intel Core i5-4570 CPU (3.20 GHz, 4 GB RAM) running Windows 7 Enterprise with service pack 1. VLC media player was used to access the files.
The collection contains files in the following formats:
Tagged Image File Format[.tif]
MPEG-4 Part 14 [.mp4]
An unknown individual transferred the collection to the Archives prior to 1989. The Estate of Gene Schuttey donated accession 2007-021 in September 2007. The department transferred additional materials in November 2015 (accession 2015-009) and February 2016 (accession 2015-033).
Contents List
- Records, 1911-2015, UWM Archival Collection 85; 14.3 cubic ft. (23 boxes)
  - 1. Administrative Files, 1946-2002
    Materials are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Academic Program and Curriculum Committee Review, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Actor's Equity Association, 1989, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Employment, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Alumni, Frost, Lindsay, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Alumni, Jorgensen, Kim, 1982-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Alumni, Love, Victor, 1986-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Alumni News Articles, 1978-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Alumni, Rensenhouse, John, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Season, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Updates 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - American Players Theatre, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - American Summer Theatre Festival, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Brecht Symposium, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Budget
      - 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 1990-2000 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
    - Christmas Community Tour, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Cobalt Trip, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence
      - 1962-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1-11)
      - 1966-1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Eastern Europe, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Hungary, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Office of the Dean, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - South Korea, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Sweden, 1962-1972 and 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Cornerstone Performing Arts Hall, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Department of Theatre Degree Program, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Department Meeting Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
    - DePaul, James (University Theatre Director), 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - El Paso Trip, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Festival Istropolitana in Bratislava, Czechoslovakia, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Graduate Program, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Program Review, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Graduates, 1992-1995, 2006, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Guest Artists, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Handbook for Students, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Harry W. Schwartz Bookshop Promotional Readings, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - High School Matinees, 1986-2002 (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theater Arts, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - International Dimensions, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - International Pamphlets, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - International Studies Program Committee, 1990-1991, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - International Theatre Institute, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - International Theatre Training Conference, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - International Theatre Training Festival in Izmir, Turkey, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - International Theatre Training Festival in Milwaukee, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - International Theatre Training Festival in Sydney, Australia, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - International Theatre Training Workshop, Greek Project, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Japan Trip, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Miller Theater Contract, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Milwaukee Repertory Theater, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Mrozek Festival in Krakow, Poland, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - National Collegiate Players, 1954-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - North German Theatre Festival, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Northern Stage Company
      - 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Actors, undated (Box 4, Folder 11-14)
      - Actresses, undated (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
    - Paris and Virgin Islands Tour, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Photographs
      - Actors' Portraits, 1978-1987, undated (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
      - American Players Theatre, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Costume Design, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - Department of Theatre Arts Candids, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Enters, Warren, Summer Director, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Lake Michigan Playhouse, 1952-1953, undated (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
      - Mrozek Festival, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Staff, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Students, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Students, Set Constructions, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Theatre, 1957, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Theatre Workshop, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Planning Documents, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
    - Production Season Overviews
      - 1956-1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - 1982-1987 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - 2000-2015 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Professional Theatre Training Program
      - News Articles, 1976-1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Poster, undated (Box 23)
    - Recruitment Brochures and Advertising, 1989-2002 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
    - Shanghai Trip, 1998, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Summer Drama Workshop, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Summer in the Park
      - 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
      - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Advisory Board, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Articles and Promotions, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Course 524 Project, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - June 24th Opening Reception, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Mailing Records, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Neighborhood Opposition, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Receptions, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Wrap-Up, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sweden Trip, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Ten Chimneys Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Theater Company
      - A Midsummer Night's Dream Script, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Our Town Script and Music, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Premiere Season Materials, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Publicity, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Summer Staff and Company Selection, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Theater On Campus, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Theater-Speech Curricula, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Tours of Milwaukee High Schools, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University Players, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University/Resident Theatre Association, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - World Theatre Training Institute (WTTI)
      - 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Vienna Conference, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 2. Production Files, 1911-2015, The production photographs consist of a mix of 8x10, 5x7, 4x6, and 3x5 sizes. Unless otherwise stated, all of the negatives are 35 mm safety film.
    Materials are arranged chronologically by production season and thereafter alphabetically by production title. Brochures and fliers are in boxes 1-11, photographs in boxes 12-18, slides in box 19, negatives in boxes 20-22, posters in box 23, and blueprints in oversize folders 1-5.
    - 1911-1940
      - Julius Caesar, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Pillars of Society, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - A Proposal Under Difficulties, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - A Rose o'Plymouth Town, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Spreading the News, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - A Winterfest, April 1911 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Sweet Lavender, April 1912 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Rivals, May 1913 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Gettysburg the Antick, June 1913 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - A Happy Pair and A Pair of Lunatics, September 1913 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The School Mistress, June 1914 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - A Nice Quiet Chat, July 1914 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Harry Lauder Songs, July 1914 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - On His Devoted Head, July 1914 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - A Twig of Thorn, March 1915 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Kindling, circa May 1915-May 1919 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Road to Yesterday, May 1915 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Ring, January 1916 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Why the Chimes Rang, December 1916 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Strongheart, January 1917 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Continental Congress, April 1917 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Voysey Inheritance, June 1917 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Flower Shop, circa October 1918-October 1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Blossoming of Mary Anne, June 1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Le Bourgeois Gentilhomme, December 1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - La Malade Imaginaire (The Imaginary Invalid), November 1921 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Maker of Dreams, January 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Florist Shop, January 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Melting Pot, April 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Candida, July 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Twelfth Night, July 1922 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Daddy Long-Legs, February 1923 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - The Worsted Man, circa February 1924-February 1928 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - You and I, June 1929 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Foreign Language Plays, May 1930 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Modern Foreign Language Plays, June 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1950-1959
      - Bean Blossom Hill, circa 1950-1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Let us Now Praise Famous Men, circa 1950-1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Twelfth Night, circa 1950-1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Hay Fever, circa 1950-1959
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Skin of Our Teeth, 1950-1951
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Tom Sawyer, March-May 1950
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Jack and the Beanstalk, September-December 1950
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Goodbye, My Fancy, September-November 1951
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Ah! Wilderness, March-May 1952
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Death Takes a Holiday, June-August 1952
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - The Importance of Being Earnest, June-August 1952
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Student Productions, 1953-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Male Animal, June-August 1953
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Ten Little Indians, June-August 1953
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Arms and the Man, June-August 1954
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Arsenic and Old Lace, June-August 1954
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Huckleberry Finn, October 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - The Hasty Heart, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Cry the Beloved Country, January 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Beyond the Horizon, April 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - The Tempest, April 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Doctor Knock, October 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - St. Joan, November 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Aladdin and the Wonderful Lamp, December 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - The River Line, February 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Winterset, March 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - The Winter's Tale, March 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Time Limit, November 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Emperor's New Clothes, December 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - The Ballad of Baby Doe, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - The Hidden River, October 1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1969
      - My Three Angels, April 1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - The Winslow Boy, October 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - The Puppet Prince, December 1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - The Deadly Game, March 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - The Enchanted, May 1961 (Box 7, Folder 9)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Theatre in 3D: The Chairs, The Lottery, and The Dock Brief, July 1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Five Finger Exercise, October 1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 20)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - School for Scandal, October 1961 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - One Act Plays, November 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - The Hunters and the Henwife, December 1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 22)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Noh Plays, January 1962 (Box 7, Folder 15)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - All the Way Home, March 1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 24)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Chitra, Picnic on the Battlefield, and "The Sucking Stones," April 1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Night of the Auk, May 1962 (Box 7, Folder 18)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 25)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - The Dumbwaiter, July 1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Pullman Car Hiawatha, July 1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - The Rainmaker, October 1962 (Box 7, Folder 20)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 26)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - An Evening with Two Irishmen, November 1962 (Box 7, Folder 21)
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Bedtime Story, November 1962
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - The Shewing-Up of Blanco Posnet, November 1962
        - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 28)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Robinson Crusoe, January 1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - The Innocents, March 1963 (Box 7, Folder 23)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - The Fantasticks, May 1963 (Box 7, Folder 24)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - The Revelation, June 1963 (Box 7, Folder 25)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
      - A Midsummer Nights Dream, November 1963 (Box 7, Folder 26)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Hodag, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Ondine, May 1964 (Box 7, Folder 28)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Huckleberry Finn, June 1964
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Henry IV, June 1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - The Queen and the Rebels, October 1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Aladdin and the Wonderful Lamp, December 1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 9)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - In White America, March 1965 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - The Physicists, March 1965 (Box 7, Folder 33)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 10)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Look Back in Anger, May 1965 (Box 7, Folder 34)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 11)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, July 1965 (Box 7, Folder 35)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 12)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - The Deputy, October 1965 (Box 7, Folder 36)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - East of the Sun West of the Moon, November 1965 (Box 7, Folder 37)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - One Act x Four, December 1965 (Box 7, Folder 38)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Enrico IV, January 1966 (Box 7, Folder 39)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Winter's Tale, March 1966 (Box 7, Folder 40)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 17)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - The Happy Haven, May 1966 (Box 7, Folder 41)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 18)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - The Killer, July 1966 (Box 7, Folder 42)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 19)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Love's Labour's Lost, October 1966 (Box 7, Folder 43)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 20)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Saturday Theatre and Noonday Theatre, October 1966 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - The Trial, December 1966 (Box 7, Folder 45)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Billy the Kid, January 1967
        - Negatives (Box 20)
      - The Merry Pranks of Tyll, February 1967 (Box 7, Folder 46)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - Slides (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Good Woman of Setzuan, March 1967 (Box 7, Folder 47)
        - Blueprints (Oversize 1)
        - Negatives (Box 20)
        - Negatives, 2x2 safety film (Box 22)
        - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Sir Tyrone Guthrie Lecture, March 1967
        - Negatives (Box 20)